Quick actions[Plans](https://www.tunemymusic.com/plans)[Help](https://www.tunemymusic.com/help)

English

عربي

čeština

繁體中文

简体中文

Español

Français

Dansk

Deutsch

Nederlandse

Tagalog

עברית

हिन्दी

Magyar

日本語

Indonesia

Italiano

한국어

Norsk

Polski

Português

Română

Русский

Svenska

Türk

ไทย

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. It is TuneMyMusic's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, [https://www.tunemymusic.com](https://www.tunemymusic.com/).  
  
We don\`t collect any personal information. We only ask for information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.  
  
To improve your experience on our site, we may use 'cookies'. Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  
  
TuneMyMusic’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.  
  
TuneMyMusic uses the [YouTube API Services](https://developers.google.com/youtube/terms/api-services-terms-of-service). Please also checkout [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). TuneMyMusic uses YouTube user information to access, provide and display YouTube datas on TuneMyMusic. TuneMyMusic will be able to retrieve user YouTube username, user private playlists, liked videos, uploaded videos and subscribed channels. User datas are only used to provide TuneMyMusic services and are not shared with any external service. You can always revoke TuneMyMusic access to your data via the [Google security settings page](https://myaccount.google.com/permissions?pli=1) and can also contact TuneMyMusic with any questions or complaints [here](https://www.tunemymusic.com/contact-us).  
  
TuneMyMusic uses the [Spotify API Services](https://developer.spotify.com/terms/). Please also checkout [Spotify Privacy Policy](https://www.spotify.com/il-he/legal/privacy-policy/). TuneMyMusic uses Spotify user information to access, provide and display Spotify datas on TuneMyMusic. TuneMyMusic will be able to retrieve user Spotify username, user private playlists, liked tracks, liked albums and liked artists. User datas are only used to provide TuneMyMusic services and are not shared with any external service. You can always revoke TuneMyMusic access to your data via the [Spotify Apps with access to your Spotify information page](https://www.spotify.com/il-he/account/apps/) and can also contact TuneMyMusic with any questions or complaints [here](https://www.tunemymusic.com/contact-us).  
  
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.  
  
We use the “Custom Audience pixel” of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”) on our website. With its help, we can keep track of what users do after they see or click on a Facebook advertisement. This enables us to monitor the effectiveness of Facebook ads for purposes of statistics and market research. Data collected in this way is anonymous to us, which means we cannot see the personal data of individual users. However, this data is saved and processed by Facebook. Facebook can connect this data with your Facebook account and use it for its own advertising purposes, in accordance with Facebook’s Data Policy which can be found at [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). You can allow Facebook and its partners to place ads on and outside of Facebook. A cookie can also be saved on your device for these purposes.  
  
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
  
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.  
  
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.  
  
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.  
  
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

### Always happy to help you

Feel free to ask any questions

Tune My Music

Help

Legal
